

Salutations, and many thanks to you; my name is

JARED CHRISTENSEN

а

WEB & GRAPHIC DESIGNER

with a love for typography, music and gaming.

As a well-rounded user experience designer, I make sure that systems, interfaces, language and graphics are human-friendly, emotive, aesthetically pleasing, clear, on-brand and usable — with a touch of mellow smoothness. I have brought my knowledge and skills to bear on projects for clients ranging from Fortune 50 companies to bootstrapped startups.

I am primarily a Visual Designer with information architecture and interaction design skills.

This means I mostly deal with pretty pretty pictures in Photoshop, though I have a working knowledge of research techniques, wireframing, testing, and front-end web development. JavaScript is still a black box to me. A sexy, enticing black box which I will one day unwrap.



EXPERIENCE

FREELANCE WORK

Designer

Produced visual designs, logos, icons, and HTML & CSS code for various small clients.

VIEWZI

Visual Designer (June 2008 \sim) Dallas, TX

Produced visual and interface design for the Viewzi application shell, Views and some marketing & pitch-related materials.

BRIGHT CORNER, GENIANT & EMC

Visual Designer (May 2005 ~ June 2008) Dallas, TX

(I started at Bright Corner, which was acquired by Geniant in 2006, which was acquired by EMC in 2007.)

Produced visual and interface designs, some web development, information architecture, interaction design, icon design and some identity/logo design. Clients included Handango, eInstruction, Backgroundchecks.com, Turner Construction and American State Bank.

G2E SERVICES

Senior Web Designer (May 2003 ~ May 2005) San Antonio, TX

Produced visual design & web development, information architecture, Flash development and copywriting. Also participated heavily in logo design and assisted in much of the print design workload. Clients included The City of San Antonio and The City of Eagle Pass.

REDGIZMO

Web & Graphic Designer (Oct. 2002 ~ April 2003) San Antonio, TX

Designed & developed websites, 3D models & animations, e-newsletters and PDF documents. Developed web media for ad agencies Bromley Communications & Garcia 360.

PROSAN INTERACTIVE MEDIA

Web Designer (May 2000 \sim Jan. 2001) San Antonio, TX

Designed & developed Flash websites for local businesses.

WORK

Examples of my work can be found at my personal website, JAREDIGITAL.COM/PORTFOLIO. Additional, NDA-protected, work can be provided on request.

SKILLSET

Visual Design, User Experience Design, Interaction Design, Information Architecture, Illustration, Writing, and an understanding of front-end code and back-end technologies.

EDUCATION

San Antonio College ~ San Antonio, TX Associate in Applied Science, Graphic Arts - Electronic Graphics

SXSW 2006 SXSW 2007 SXSW 2008 Webmaster Jam Session 2006 Webmaster Jam Session 2007

AWARDS & RECOGNITIONS

2005 ~ Gold ADDY Award, BlueStarOintment.com 2005 ~ Gold ADDY Award, G2EServices.com 2005 ~ Special Judges ADDY Award for BlueStarOintment.com

Jaredigital.com has been featured on a number of web design showcases and galleries. An (mostly) up-to-date listing of features can be found at claimid.com/jaredigital.

CONTACT

Jared Christensen jaredc@jaredigital.com

Thank you. —